<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>pleb.fi on the most pleb conf</title><link>https://pleb.fi/</link><description>Recent content in pleb.fi on the most pleb conf</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pleb.fi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>fees &amp; smart contracts</title><link>https://pleb.fi/transcripts/2021/miami/ryang/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pleb.fi/transcripts/2021/miami/ryang/</guid><description>Jeremy Rubin 0:00 Let&amp;rsquo;s give a big thank you to Tarun for that that was really, really awesome. And are you gonna be able to stick around for a bit? I&amp;rsquo;ll be around, I will have some brainstorming session too. So you can catch them with your questions. And he&amp;rsquo;s @tarunChitra on Twitter. So definitely follow there and tweet at him if you got any other questions.
Jeremy Rubin 0:21 I think that stuff is it&amp;rsquo;s a pretty critical, like soul searching question for the Bitcoin community.</description></item><item><title>tradfi v.s. defi: they won't or they can't?</title><link>https://pleb.fi/transcripts/2021/miami/tarun/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pleb.fi/transcripts/2021/miami/tarun/</guid><description>Tarun Chitra 0:00 Thanks, Jeremy, for the introduction. Yeah, so I think what I&amp;rsquo;m going to really cover is kind of like, what makes DeFi markets different than traditional finance markets and when you&amp;rsquo;re developing what, what things you should be thinking of. But I think part of that is actually looking at what the overall market structure looks like, and why some of these markets are just significantly more efficient, or have created, you know, this huge amount of demand over the last 12 months.</description></item><item><title>pleb.fi austin</title><link>https://pleb.fi/austin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pleb.fi/austin/</guid><description>pleb.fi /austin in austin august 21st-22nd
(weekend before bitblockboom dallas) bring your pajamas (there&amp;rsquo;s a hackathon) Tweet our lovely event sponsors trammell venture partners
lnpay
judica
lincoln network
unchained capital
sphinx.chat
anon supporter &amp;lt;3
voltage cloud
fulgur ventures
larry chiang
staking.dog
fold
casa
galaxy digital
amanda fabiano
key dates see below for exact agenda.
sat 21st august day: workshops + talks sat 21st august evening: hackathon kickoff sunday 22nd august day: hackathon sunday 22nd august evening: hackathon demos other fun around the event pleb.</description></item><item><title>pleb.fi disclaimers</title><link>https://pleb.fi/disclaimers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pleb.fi/disclaimers/</guid><description>Disclaimers And Rules Code of Conduct The organizers of pleb.fi want these events to be a safe, respectful, and productive environment for everyone. This is an intelligent and well-intended community, and we as the workshop committee are not inclined to tell people what to do. To that end, this code of conduct spells out the behavior we support and don&amp;rsquo;t support at our events and by attending you agree to abide by it.</description></item><item><title>pleb.fi miami</title><link>https://pleb.fi/miami/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pleb.fi/miami/</guid><description>pleb.fi /miami ???Looking for 2022??? never stop improvin bitcoin,
but specifically on june 6th 2021 in miami think outside the box june 6th, 2021, miami at a secret location, 12-5pm. not the best. not the brightest. the plebs. like 50 of them. come for a day of hacking, mentorship, workshops, and discussions on how to contribute to bitcoin functionality accelerationism and build decentralized finance applications on bitcoin. we'll also get into how to get your project funded either traditionally or through new age pleb means.</description></item><item><title>pleb.fi miami 2022</title><link>https://pleb.fi/miami2022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pleb.fi/miami2022/</guid><description>pleb.fi /miami2022 🎶 the plebs are back in town🎶 badder BIGGER but most importantly&amp;hellip; PLEBBER april 4-5th 2022 in miami (hialeah area) its sapioszn get in loser we&amp;rsquo;re buidling if you dont come you will have to turn in your pleb card come for 2 days of hacking, mentorship, workshops, and discussions on how to contribute to bitcoin functionality accelerationism and build kickass applications on bitcoin using sapio, taproot, ctv, and more.</description></item><item><title>pleb.fi miami 2023</title><link>https://pleb.fi/miami2023/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pleb.fi/miami2023/</guid><description>pleb.fi /miami2023 🎶 guess who&amp;rsquo;s back 🎶 back again PLEBFI&amp;rsquo;S BACK BACK AGAIN PLEBFISBACKPLEBFISBACK PLEBFISBACKPLEBFISBACK may 16-17 in Wynnwood
its bankLESS season if you dont come you will have to turn in your pleb card come for 2 days of hacking, mentorship, workshops, and discussions on how to contribute to bitcoin functionality accelerationism and build kickass applications on bitcoin using nostr, fedimint, miniscript, and more. we&amp;rsquo;ll also get into how to get your project funded either traditionally or through new age pleb means.</description></item></channel></rss>