<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Transcripts from PlebFi Miami on the most pleb conf</title><link>https://pleb.fi/transcripts/2020/miami/</link><description>Recent content in Transcripts from PlebFi Miami on the most pleb conf</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pleb.fi/transcripts/2020/miami/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>fees &amp; smart contracts</title><link>https://pleb.fi/transcripts/2020/miami/ryang/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pleb.fi/transcripts/2020/miami/ryang/</guid><description>Jeremy Rubin 0:00 Let&amp;rsquo;s give a big thank you to Tarun for that that was really, really awesome. And are you gonna be able to stick around for a bit? I&amp;rsquo;ll be around, I will have some brainstorming session too. So you can catch them with your questions. And he&amp;rsquo;s @tarunChitra on Twitter. So definitely follow there and tweet at him if you got any other questions.
Jeremy Rubin 0:21 I think that stuff is it&amp;rsquo;s a pretty critical, like soul searching question for the Bitcoin community.</description></item><item><title>tradfi v.s. defi: they won't or they can't?</title><link>https://pleb.fi/transcripts/2020/miami/tarun/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pleb.fi/transcripts/2020/miami/tarun/</guid><description>Tarun Chitra 0:00 Thanks, Jeremy, for the introduction. Yeah, so I think what I&amp;rsquo;m going to really cover is kind of like, what makes DeFi markets different than traditional finance markets and when you&amp;rsquo;re developing what, what things you should be thinking of. But I think part of that is actually looking at what the overall market structure looks like, and why some of these markets are just significantly more efficient, or have created, you know, this huge amount of demand over the last 12 months.</description></item></channel></rss>